We won't come down for later on, watching the world spinning around, bringing you closer like ties to the moon
The sun is setting, but we're just beginning, it's feeling spinning, I'm forever winning
With you by my side, I know we'll never hide from the love that we found under summer sound
Summer love, it's more than a season, you're the reason I'm breathing
We're not leaving, we're staying forever like the ties to the moon, we'll be together
Yeah, yeah
Now the leaves are falling and the air is cold, but our love is burning, never growing old
We made a promise under the August moon that our summer love will never be through, forever summer, forever you and I
Under the same sky, never saying goodbye
Summer love, summer love
Take a walk around the beach, put your feet in the sand, don't you be scared, hold your head
Nothing can describe a feeling that I'm feeling I'm with you forever more, I'll never forget you
Baby, you can be my summer love
I want to buy what you want to get high, but you get in the car and drive with you
Baby, can you be my summer love
In room clouds puffing on loud, we won't come down for later on
Watching the world spinning around bring you closer like ties to the moon
Take a walk around the beach, put your feet in the sand, don't you be scared, hold your head
Nothing can describe a feeling that I'm feeling I'm with you forever more, I'll never forget you
Baby, you can be my summer love
I want to buy what you want to get high, but you get in the car and drive with you
Baby, can you be my summer love
I want to buy what you want to get high, but you get in the car